Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
- Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union. Local 65, Publication (Box 415, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Notes on 'We build as we fight, the Officers': Report to the Third Biennial Convention, 1948; Publication (Box 415, Folder 1)
- Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union., Publication (Box 415, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Your group insurance plan, 1945; Publication (Box 415, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Security, 1949; Publication (Box 415, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: In the matter of the Arbitration between F.W. Woolworth Company and Wholesale & Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1946; Publication (Box 415, Folder 2)
- Womens' Educational and Industrial Union, Publication (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 47th Annual report, 1925; Publication (Box 415, Folder 3)
    Author: Womens' Educational and Industrial Union
  - Item 2: Course in vocational guidance, 1916; Publication (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: outiline, 1906; Publication (Box 415, Folder 3)
    Author: Massachusetts Administration of Labour Law
  - Item 4: Housing costs and choices of the older consumer, 1960; Publication (Box 415, Folder 3)
    Author: Constance Williams
  - Item 5: Injunction threat ends sit-in strike, 1946; Publication (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Local 65 seeks to block polls set by NLRB, 1946; Publication (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Truck union backs sit-in strikes, 1946; Publication (Box 415, Folder 3)
- National Women's Trade Union League of America, Publication (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Miss Schneiderman hailed on retirement; Mrs. P.J. Blackstone, Trade-union Official; Trade Union League program; Women's Union League to end after 47 years; Woman Unionist to quit post here; Women's place in labor unions, 1949-1950 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Mrs. P.J. Blackstone, Trade-union Official, 1949-1950 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Trade Union League program, 1949-1950 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Women's Union League to end after 47 years, 1949-1950 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Woman Unionist to quit post here, 1949-1950 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Women's place in labor unions, 1949-1950 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The Misses Smith go to Washington, 1940; Publication (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: An Experiment in education; The Progress of Industry; Professional Women, Business Women, Industrial Women, 1909; Publication (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: An Experiment in education; The Progress of Industry; Professional Women, Business Women, Industrial Women, 1928; Publication (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: An Experiment in education; The Progress of Industry; Professional Women, Business Women, Industrial Women, Publication (Box 416, Folder 1)
- National Women's Trade Union League of America, Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Life and Labor Bulletin, 1928; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
    Author: National Women's Trade Union League of America
    Notes: v.6:no.8 (1928)
  - Item 2: Life and Labor Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.107 (1949)
  - Item 3: 1929 Convention, Wage Symposium Outline, Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The Five-Day work week, Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
    Author: Agnes Nestor
  - Item 5: Address of Mrs. Raymond Robins, President of the National Womensto the Seventh Biennial Convention, 1919; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
    Author: Margaret Dreier Robins
  - Item 6: Address of Mrs. Raymond Robins, President of the National Womensto the Sixth Biennial Convention, 1917; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Special Report submitted to the Fourth Convention of the., 1913; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
    Author: Organisation of Women Workers in Germany
  - Item 8: An appeal to the union women, Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
    Author: Mary E. McDowell
  - Item 9: Fourth Biennial Convention, 1913; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: School for Active Workers in the Labor Movement, 1915; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Why is it, What is it, Who it is, Where it is, 1911; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Why should you vote for Hoover, Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Report of Committee on Women's Work in Wartime - ..Sixth Biennial Convention, 1917; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Convention, 1909; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
    Notes: Handbook
  - Item 15: Address of the President, Mrs. Raymond Robins to the Third Congress, 1923; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: The Children's Amendment, 1924; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: How to organize: a problem. Resume of findings, one day institute on trade union organization, 1929; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Educational plans of the National Women's Trade Union League, 1914; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Self-government in the workshop, 1903; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: The Strike of the steel workers: a few facts in the ninth week of the strike., 1919; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Report of Interstate Conference of the National Women's Trade Union League, held September 26-28, 1908, in New York., Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: English women in the labor and co-operative movements, 1915; Publication (Box 416, Folder 2)
- United States. Women's Bureau, Publication (Box 416, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Toward better working conditions for women, 1953; Publication (Box 416, Folder 3)
    Author: United States. Women's Bureau
- New York Women's Trade Union League, Publication (Box 416, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Questions for a labor quiz, 1939; Publication (Box 416, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: League Bulletin, 1940-1950 (Box 416, Folder 4)
    Author: New York Women's Trade Union League
    Notes: Feb. 1940, 1942, 1949 -1950
  - Item 3: Bulletin, 1950-1955 (Box 416, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Life and Labor Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 416, Folder 4)
- Womens Trade Union League, Publication (Box 416, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Help wanted!, 1939; Publication (Box 416, Folder 5)
    Author: Cara Cook
  - Item 2: Monthly Bulletin, 1928; Publication (Box 416, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.4-6, 12 (1928)
  - Item 3: Monthly Bulletin, 1929; Publication (Box 416, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.9:no.1-6, 10 (1929)
  - Item 4: Monthly Bulletin, 1930; Publication (Box 416, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.10:no.1-3, 5-6, 11 (1930)
- New York Women's Trade Union League, Publication (Box 416, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Completing of mission closes clubhouse of the Women's Trade Union League here, 1955; Publication (Box 416, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Annual Election of Officers Polls open 12 noon to 10 pm, 1951; Publication (Box 416, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Bulletin, 1951-1954 (Box 416, Folder 6)
- Womens Trade Union League, Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Educational work of the National Women's Trade Union League, Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
    Author: Alice Henry
  - Item 2: Summary report of the full report of the New York Women's Trade Union League to the., 1947; Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Annual Report, 1948-1949 (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Education Program, 1946-1947 (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: After the day's work, Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Leisure time activities, Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: To Unions in the New York City Area and Cooperating Organizing, Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Annual Report, 1931-1932 (Box 416, Folder 7)
    Author: Women's Trade Union League of New York
  - Item 9: Women's Trade Union League of New York, Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Help wanted!, 1939; Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: White Collar and Professional Workers who speaks up for you?, 1950; Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Library of the Women's Trade Unio League, 1909; Publication (Box 416, Folder 7)
- National Women's Trade Union League of America, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: After the day's work, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Convention, 1911; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
    Notes: Handbook. Second copy
  - Item 3: Truths and half-truths about child labor, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Services and activities, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The voice of labor: A selection of verses, 1919; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
    Notes: A selection of verses, written by members of the Women's Trade Union League, as they appeared from time to time in Life and labor and in other League publications, May 1, 1919.
  - Item 6: Action needed!: post-war jobs for women, 1944; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Some facts regarding unorganized working women in the sweated industries, 1914; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: The eight-hour day for women, 1915; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Training school for women organizers of the National Women's Trade Union League of America, 1914; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: The history of trade unionism among women in Boston., 1906; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
    Author: Edith Abbott
  - Item 11: The conditions of women workers in the hotel and restaurant industry, 1935; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Interstate conference called by the Women's Trade., 1916; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: The 48-hour week for women, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Report of Committee on Women's Work in Wartime - ..Sixth Biennial Convention, 1917; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Articles on the Early History of Women Trad Unionists of America by Ruth Delzell, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
    Author: Ruth Delzell
  - Item 16: Are you paid by bonus?, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: The Union's on the job, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Why should I joint a Trade Union?, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: I have something to tell you, Girls, Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Women's demand for humane treatment of women workers in shop and factory by Rheta Childe Dorr, 1909; Publication (Box 416, Folder 8)
    Author: Rheta Childe Dorr
  - Item 21: Official report, 1905-1906 (Box 416, Folder 8)
- International Woodworkers of America, Publication (Box 417, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Proceedings Second Annual Convention, 1949; Publication (Box 417, Folder 1)
    Author: International Woodworkers of America. District Council No. 4
  - Item 2: Request for bargaining data, 1954; Publication (Box 417, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Health and Welfare Program, 1954; Publication (Box 417, Folder 1)
    Author: International Woodworkers of America.
  - Item 4: Your Union has a public, Publication (Box 417, Folder 1)
    Author: International Woodworkers of America
  - Item 5: Right to work laws: public federal frauds, 1956; Publication (Box 417, Folder 1)
    Author: Jerome Leo Toner
  - Item 6: How to be a union reporter, 1953; Publication (Box 417, Folder 1)
- International Woodworkers of America, Publication (Box 417, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Uniting and serving workers in all branches of the wood-producing and wood-using industry of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 417, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report on the current dispute in Newfoundland between the International Woodworkers..and The United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, 1961; Publication (Box 417, Folder 2)
    Author: Newfoundland Federation of Labor
  - Item 3: Report to the Twelfth Annual Constitutional Convention, 1948; Publication (Box 417, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Forestry Program, Twelfth Annual Constitutional Convention, 1948; Publication (Box 417, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Turmoil in the woods: a report on the dispute between the International Woodworkers of America and the Anglo-Newfoundland Development Company Limited, 1959; Publication (Box 417, Folder 2)
- International Woodworkers of America, Publication (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: We'd like to meet the woodworkers, 1945; Publication (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: I.W.A. labor statistics, lumber industry, 1949; Publication (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Know your union, 1948; Publication (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Your union, 1946; Publication (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Bargaining for the union: a discussion for IWA job stewards and committeemen., 1950; Publication (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Manual, revised November, 1949, Publication (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Shop Steward: key to a strong union, 1941; Publication (Box 417, Folder 3)
- International Woodworkers of America, Publication (Box 417, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Meet the woodworkers, 1950-1959 (Box 417, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Negotiating a working agreement, 1950-1959 (Box 417, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Worker Education Conference Minutes: Friday, December 5, 1952: ERB Memorial Student Union - University of Oregon, Publication (Box 417, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: It's your union!, 1950-1959 (Box 417, Folder 4)
- International Woodworkers of America, Publication (Box 417, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Meet the woodworkers: on his job in his union, Publication (Box 417, Folder 5)
- International Woodworkers of America, Publication (Box 417, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Reports on labor relations, social, and economic trends, 1953-1954 (Box 417, Folder 6)
    Author: International Woodworkers of America. Dept. of Research
    Notes: v.1:no.6,7-12 (1953-1954)
  - Item 2: Reports on labor relations, social, and economic trends, 1954-1955 (Box 417, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.2:no.1-12 (1954-1955)
  - Item 3: International Woodworkers of America: means -better wages - better working conditions - job and economic security - shorter hours, Publication (Box 417, Folder 6)
- International Woodworkers of America, Publication (Box 417, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Work, 1939; Publication (Box 417, Folder 7)
    Author: Workers Alliance of America
    Notes: v.1:no.23; v.2:no.3. very brittle
  - Item 2: From the ground up, 1946; Publication (Box 417, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Correspondence - The present cry for reducing the WPZ and relief appropriations in order to balance the budget at the expense of the unemplyed., 1937; Publication (Box 417, Folder 7)
    Author: Workers Alliance of Greater New York
  - Item 4: Resolution on the Boileau Bill, Publication (Box 417, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Organizational manual of the Unemployed Division of the Workers Alliance of Greater New York, 1937; Publication (Box 417, Folder 7)
    Author: Robert Friedman
  - Item 6: $60 at 60 pension plan: minimum security for senior citizens, 1939; Publication (Box 417, Folder 7)
- Workers (Communist) party of America, Publication (Box 417, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: From the third through the fourth convention of the Workers (Communist) party of America, 1926; Publication (Box 417, Folder 8)
    Author: Charles E. Ruthenberg
  - Item 2: For a labor party., 1923; Publication (Box 417, Folder 8)
    Author: John Pepper
    Notes: Recent revolutionary changes in American politics
  - Item 3: Stop the enemies of the working people: a program for the Detroit elections, 1947; Publication (Box 417, Folder 8)
- International Workers Defense League, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Just opening doors is not enough, 1966; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: WDL News, 1963-1965 (Box 417, Folder 9)
    Author: Workers Defense League
  - Item 3: Correpsondence - I know you've been concerned, as I have been, about recent incidents involving Negro and Puerto Rican youth, 1966; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The following is a statement presented at the White House today by a National Delegation of 500 representatives of the unemployed and WPA Workers, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: News Bulletin, 1938; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
    Notes: January 1938.
  - Item 6: Correspondence - As an old friend and supporter of the Workers Defense League; Rarely do I request funds for organizations not directly involved in the Southern Struggle., 1965-1966 (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Workers Defense Bulletin, 1943; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Not only to preserve the past but to enrich the future, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Will we deport thesse young men to the South African apartheid life of discrimination, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: The Ferment for freedom, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Breaking the barrier in the Building Trades Unions, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: For the defense, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Workers Defense League, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Where would you go?, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Urge hearings on security risk program, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: With force and violence, 1920; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
    Author: Ben Legers
  - Item 17: correspondence - Thank you very much for your contribution during 1969, Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: The WDL Apprenticeship Training Program: Report of a year's experiment, 1965; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Oxman perjury plot, 1917; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
    Author: Robert Minor
  - Item 20: What's behind the "Christian Front"?, 1939; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
    Author: Norman Thomas
  - Item 21: Hagueism is fascism, 1938; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - Item 22: Jobs without creed or color, 1945; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
    Author: Winifred Raushenbush
  - Item 23: Labor, defense, and democracy, 1941; Publication (Box 417, Folder 9)
    Author: Robert M. La Follette; Elinore M. Herrick; James B. Carey
- International Workers Defense League, Publication (Box 417, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labor, defense, and democracy, 1941; Publication (Box 417, Folder 10)
- Workers Education Bureau of America, Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Conference on New relationships between Labor and Capital, 1929; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Workers Education in the United States, 1922; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: An interview with James H. Maurer, Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
    Author: James H. Maurer
  - Item 4: Books for workerspublications of the Workers Education Bureau of America, 1949; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: A reading list of The American Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: How to start workers' study classes, 1925; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
    Author: Broadus Mitchell
  - Item 7: Primer of housing, 1927; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
    Author: Arthur Cort Holden; Clarence S. Stein; William J. Tracy
  - Item 8: High wages, the basis of recovery, 1935; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
    Author: Henry Ford; Edward A. Filene; Robert W. Johnson; Matthew Woll
    Notes: Opinions of Henry Ford, Edward A. Filene, Robert W. Johnson [and others] Foreword and open letter by Matthew Woll.
  - Item 9: How to run a union meeting: a simple manual on parliamentary law, 1948; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
    Author: Paul Blanshard
    Notes: 11th edition, revised. 2 copies
  - Item 10: Shop steward's manual, 1947; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
    Author: Barbara Briggs; Lois Remmers
  - Item 11: United textile workers of America, 1926; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Workers' study groups, 1935; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
    Author: Workers Education Bureau of America
  - Item 13: Labor forums: a brief manual on the conduct of labor forums, 1935; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: The shop steward: an outline of his work in the union, 1935; Publication (Box 418, Folder 1)
    Notes: Prepared by Federal Labor Union No. 18677, Detroit
- Workers Education Bureau of America, Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Brookwood: Bulletin and Announcement of courses, 1927, Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Education of the worker is the hope of America, 1926; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Report of the Executive Committee to the Biennial convention of the, 1948; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Workers' Education and labor leadership, 1935; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: Fannia M. Cohn
    Notes: Article. Reprinted for Workers Education Bureau of America
  - Item 5: Labor fights bigotry, 1943; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: Mark Starr
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Prophetic Religion. 2 copies
  - Item 6: Workers' education in the United States (reprinted for Workers' Education Bureau of America), 1934; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Labor and education - address delivered before the 57th Annual Convention, 1937; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: Spencer Miller
  - Item 8: Labor and International Relations, 1932; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Labor speaks for itself!, 1936; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: The pioneer institute of labor, an experiment in understanding, 1945; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: Spencer Miller, Jr.; Ruth Taylor
    Notes: A fifteen-year review of Rutgers labor institute against a background of the news, 1931-1945.
  - Item 11: Democracy and civil liberties, 1938; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: American Federation of Labor
    Notes: A list of the resolutions, actions, and official declarations of The American Federation of Labor on democracy and civil liberties from 1881-1938.
  - Item 12: Economic security; a study of community needs and resources, 1951; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: John Wilkinson McConnell; Robert Risley
  - Item 13: American workers' education: its meaning, methods, and policies, 1936; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: Mollie Ray Carroll; Spencer Miller, Jr.
  - Item 14: An American adventure in workers' education, 1936; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: Charles A. Beard
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Workers' Education, Fifteenth Anniversary Issue. 2 copies
  - Item 15: First steps in public speaking for labor union member: a three-months course for home study, 1938; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: John Mantle Clapp
  - Item 16: The pros and cons of consumer credit, 1941; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: Mrs. Constance Kent
  - Item 17: Workers' education, 1927; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: Arthur Gleason; Spence Miller, Jr.
  - Item 18: The industrial future of New England, 1930; Publication (Box 418, Folder 2)
    Author: New England Labor Congress
    Notes: Proceedings of the first New England Labor Congress held in Worcester, Mass., October 25-27, 1929.
- Workers' Educational Association, Publication (Box 418, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Hints on how to build your union meetings, 1948; Publication (Box 418, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Annual Report: South Western District, 1927-1928 (Box 418, Folder 3)
    Author: Worker's Educational Association
    Notes: 9th
  - Item 3: Annual Report: Western District, 1927-1928 (Box 418, Folder 3)
    Notes: 17th
  - Item 4: Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 418, Folder 3)
    Author: Worder's Educational Association
    Notes: no.8
  - Item 5: What's cookin?, 1942; Publication (Box 418, Folder 3)
    Author: George Hoadley
    Notes: Compiled from a speech given before a WEA Institute held in St. Catharines, Ont.
  - Item 6: Local democracy: developments, dangers, and opportunities in local government, 1947; Publication (Box 418, Folder 3)
    Author: E. M. Hutchinson
- Workers' Educational Association of Canada, Publication (Box 418, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Paying the shot for what?, Publication (Box 418, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Labour fact briefs "the Worker's Diplomat", Publication (Box 418, Folder 4)